Finding Aid for Sara Stillman negatives, 1995-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Sara Stillman negatives
1995-1998
Stillman, Sara
0592 Aa 2
Sara Stillman was a photographer for the Michigan Daily from 1995 to 1998. The majority of the collection consists of 35mm negatives of University of Michigan athletics, particularly football and basketball, as well as other University of Michigan and Ann Arbor events.
1 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Sara Stillman (Donor no. 9587 ) in April 2005.
The collection is open to research.
Sara Stillman was a photographer from 1995 to 1998 for the Michigan Daily, the student newspaper at the University of Michigan.
The majority of the collection consists of developed 35mm negatives, housed in protective sheets. The negatives are divided into two series: Athletics and Other Negatives. There are also a few developed photographs and rolls of undeveloped film. Three of the rolls are from a basketball game and the remainder are unidentified.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
University of Michigan--Basketball.Basketball.; University of Michigan--Football.Football.; University of Michigan--Hockey.Hockey.; University of Michigan--Baseball.Baseball.; University of Michigan--Softball.Softball.; University of Michigan--Wrestling.Wrestling.; University of Michigan--Swimming.Swimming.; University of Michigan--Student life and customs--1990-2000.1990-2000.Student life and customs
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Athletics
  Athletics (0.75 linear feet, 1995-1998) contains 35mm negatives from a variety of University of Michigan sporting events, the majority being men's basketball, football, and ice hockey. Most of the events are for men's athletics, but also include a few women's events. The negatives are arranged alphabetically by sport and then chronologically.
  - Basketball, Men's
    - University of Michigan vs. Indiana University, undated; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, 2/8/1995; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Athletes in Action (AIA), 11/1/1995, 8 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Depaul University, 11/15/1995; 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Iowa, 2/13/1996; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Australian Adelaide 36ers, 11/11/1996; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ball State University, 11/26/1996; 8 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Detroit Mercy (UDM), 12/5/1996, 9 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 2/1/1997; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Indiana University, 2/16/1997; 12 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Minnesota, 2/26/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Athletes in Action (AIA), 11/3/1997, 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Western Michigan University, 11/15/1997; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Cleveland State University, 11/18/1997; 11/19/1997; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Nevada, Las Vegas (UNLV), 12/6/1997, 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Duke University 12/12/1997 and Penn State University, 1/3/1998, 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Penn State University, 1/3/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 1/10/1998; 4 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Minnesota, 2/8/1998; 9 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Indiana University, 2/22/1998; 8 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Minnesota, undated; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Purdue University, undated; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - Unidentified, 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Basketball, Women's
    - NIT Lloyd Fisher, March 1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Baseball
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, 5/10/1997; 5 sheets (Box 1)
  - Bicycle Race
    - Men's, 6/18/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Football
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Illinois, 8/31/1996; 4 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. UCLA, 9/28/1996; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Minnesota, 10/26/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 11/2/1996, 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Purdue University, 11/9/1996, 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 11/2/1996, 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, 11/23/1996; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl, 1/1/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - Jansen / AP Award, 1/3/1997; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - Media Day, 8/1997; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Colorado, 9/13/1997; 8 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Baylor University, 9/20/1997; 11 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Notre Dame, 9/27/1997; 10/5/1997; 13 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Iowa, 10/18/1997; 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 10/25/1997; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Penn State University, 11/8/1997, 10 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, 11/22/1997; 16 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl, 1/1/1998; 13 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl, 1/1/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl Fans, 1/1/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl/Hard Rock, 1/1/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Parade, 1/1/1998; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl, Universal Studios, 1/1/1998; 4 sheets (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl, Universal Studios and BEFF Bowl, 1/1/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - Jansen / AP Award, 1/3/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
    - Woodson Goes Pro, 1/9/1998, 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 1/10/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - National Championship Parade, 1/11/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
    - Unidentified, 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Gymnastics, Women's
    - 1/26/1996, 4 sheets (Box 1)
    - 1/27/1996, 5 sheets (Box 1)
  - Ice Hockey
    - University of Michigan vs. Ferris State University, 1/5/1996; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Bowling Green State University, 1/20/1996; 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ohio State University, 2/3/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Illinois at Chicago, 2/10/1996; 2/11/1996; 17 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Miami of Ohio University, 3/7/1996; 11 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Waterloo, 10/8/1996; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Western Michigan University, 10/20/1996; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Michigan State University, 11/2/1996, 5 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Ferris State University, 12/7/1996, 10 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. University of Notre Dame, 2/14/1997; 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Alaska, 3/91997, 7 sheets (Box 1)
    - Blue and White University of Michigan Intramural Game, 10/5/1997, 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - Hockey Celebration (cheering fans), 4/4/1998; 6 sheets (Box 1)
    - Hockey Pep Rally, 4/5/1998; 6 sheets (Box 1)
  - Softball
    - Softball Championships, 5/13/1995; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - University of Michigan vs. Indiana University, 5/11/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
    - Unidentified, 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Swimming, Men's
    - Championships, 3/25/1995; 8 sheets (Box 1)
  - Swimming, Women's
    - At Indianapolis, 2/22/1997; 8 sheets (Box 1)
  - Tennis, Men's
    - undated, 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Tennis, Women's
    - 4/16/1996, 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Wrestling
    - 3/21/1998, 8 sheets (Box 1)
    - 3/23/1998, 1 sheets (Box 1)
- Other Negatives
  Other Negatives (0.25 linear feet, 1995-1998) includes negatives from University of Michigan and Ann Arbor events. Most of the images relate to the arts, political events and student activities. Of special note are the negatives related to affirmative action, the pro/affirmative action organization BAMN (By Any Means Necessary) and the celebration of Martin Luther King, Jr. Day. The negatives are arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Affirmative Action Rally, 2/24/1998; 4 sheets (Box 1)
  - AFSCME Protest, 9/13/1997; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - AIDS Walk, 6/10/1995; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Alliance 4 Justice (1, 2/5/1996 (Box 1)
  - Alternative Spring Break, 7/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Laurie, 2/6/1997; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Recorder's Soc., 4/1/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Apple Orchard, 10/5/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Art Student, Working, 1/28/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Asian Students with Kids, 3/10/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - BAMN Press Conference, 10/14/1997; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Best of Ann Arbor, 4/8/1995; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Bike Repair, 10/12/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Bollinger (President Lee Bollinger) Chat, 2/17/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Bradley, Bill at Borders, 3/25/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Brick Wall, 3/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Bronze Elegance Fashion Show, 3/18/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Buchanan/Taylor, 2/18/1996; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Car Accident, 3/12/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - "Car That Drives Drunk" at Crisler Arena Parking Lot, 1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Carvelle, James, 11/1/1996, 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - City Council, 1/6/1997; undated; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Clark, Ramsey, 1/14/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Clements Library, 3/10/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Clinton panel and cafe, 2/3/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Coffee: Parking Meters, 6/5/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Comair Memorial, 5/18/1997; 7 sheets (Box 1)
  - Coming Out Day, 10/11/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Comp. Center, 5/23/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Compost Worm, 4/14/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Construction, 1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Cruz, Wilson, 10/10/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Detroit Newspaper Strike, 1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Diag, 3/10/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Drinking on Campus, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Dr. John, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival, 9/15/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Drunk Driving: Easterbrook Family, 10/27/1997; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Duderstadt at the Capital, 3/1995; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Duderstadt Dedication of the Chemistry Building, 1995-1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Elders, Jocelyn, 1/15/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Elshtain, Jean, 2/12/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Farmer's Market, 1996; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Features, Musicians and People with Umbrellas, 01/20/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Flu Vaccine and Rose Bowl Sales, 1/13/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Fountain Bubbles, 5/28/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Freshman Split Football Tickets, 8/30/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - GEO Walkout Strike and BBQ, 4/8/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Girl Scout Cookies, 2/27/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Greek Week, Limbo, 3/17/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Guchard, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Haircut, 2/6/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Hands on Museum, 1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Hash Bash, 4/1/1993; 4/1/1994; 4/1/1995; 6 sheets (Box 1)
  - Headshots: Josh, Sara, Alan and Danielle, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Headshots: MLT, Ajanny and Zrammy, 7/11/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Headshots: S.S.J. Klein and M. Schmet, 7/7/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Health Fair NNC, 10/19/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Hinshaw, Ada Sue, 9/4/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Hooks, Benjamin, MLK, 01/16/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Iraq: Town Meeting, 2/18/1998; 8 sheets (Box 1)
  - ISR, 3/24/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - ISR Staff Appreciation Lunch, 9/12/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Jonesboro Vigil, 4/7/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Juggling Club, 3/31/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Kelsey Museum, "Caught Looking at the Kelsey,", 3/11/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Kempe House Spring Clean UP, 3/18/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Law School Meeting, 3/25/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Law School Meeting/Mural, 3/18/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Louganis, Greg, 1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Luzan/Lipke Preliminary Hearing, 12/7/1995, 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - MADD Crushed Car on the Diag, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Marketoc Day, 9/19/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Mas. Farmers Market, 4/14/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - The Michigan Theatre, 4/14/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Miller, Vernice, 1/20/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - MLK Day March, 1/15/1996; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - MLK Day Signs, 1/15/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - MLK Chuck D, 1/19/1998; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - MLK March, 1/19/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Mural, 5/6/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - NBD, 4/19/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - OIP, 1/20/1998; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Online Course Guide, People, 3/31/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Panetta, Lisa, Crisler Manager, 3/17/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Parking Tickets, 6/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Patagonia, 9/2/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Pharm, Rob, undated; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Poetry Thang, 11/2/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Potters Guild Sale, 6/4/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Pow Wow, 3/26/1995; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Prayer Meeting, 1/20/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Princess Diana's Funeral, 9/6/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Prison Art, 9/6/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Ray, Marcus: Hot Tub, 2/11/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Regents and Flint, 11/16/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Rivers, Lynn and Debbie Stabinow, 1/23/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Rose Artist, 11/30/1997; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Safe House, 3/10/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Sign Language Mini Course, 2/26/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Signs, 3/25/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Spring Fashion, 2/24/1996; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Standifer, Professor James, 2/3/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Stern, Issac, 3/10/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Student Code, First Hearing, 1/27/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Tanter, Ray, 3/24/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Tax Time, 3/24/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Tree on a Car, Farmers Market, 5/3/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Trotter House Art Show, 2/3/1995; 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Valentine's Day, 2/12/1996; 3 sheets (Box 1)
  - Variety Show E.Q., 4/1/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Vortex Group, 1/20/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Weekend Study, 10/2/1997, 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - WEMU Fund Drive, 11/2/1995, 2 sheets (Box 1)
  - Women of Color Symposium, 3/18/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Women's Glee Club Rehearsal, 11/16/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Work Study, 1/13/1998; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - YMCA Bake Sale, 1/29/1996; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Zen Buddhist Temple, 4/2/1995; 1 sheets (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, 23 sheets (Box 1)
  - Unidentified Portraits (photographs), 1 folders (Box 1)
- Unprocessed Film
  - Basketball, Michigan vs. Duke, circa 12/13/96?; 3 rolls (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, black and white film, 3 rolls (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, color film, 29 rolls (Box 1)